<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tech Smasher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 08:37:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Getting Driving Licence in France</title>
		<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/driving-licence-in-france/</link>
					<comments>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/driving-licence-in-france/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 09:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[driving licence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[permis de conduire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/?p=795</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[French Drivers Need More Experience Than British Drivers but don&#8217;t take their driver&#8217;s test too seriously: The state of affairs is still not that great concerning road tests. But, there are some different approaches to this. The first and most common method for getting driving licenses in France is divided into two categories. One is &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/driving-licence-in-france/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Getting Driving Licence in France</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>French Drivers Need More Experience Than British Drivers but don&#8217;t take their driver&#8217;s test too seriously: The state of affairs is still not that great concerning road tests. But, there are some different approaches to this.</p>



<p>The first and most common method for getting driving licenses in France is divided into two categories. One is AAC (Apprentisage accompagnée Conduite) other is accompagnée. drive more than 3,000 km over at least a year, guided by one or more guides, whether or not from the family (parents). Indeed, although it is not an obligation, it is the parents who, most of the time, supervise their child. But the AAC guide can also be another member of the family or even an outside person but holding a French license for a minimum of five years. There are some methods which you won’t find on all roads. However, they are available in case you want something else. You can call any test center or even apply online.<br>There are two ways your driving license can be changed whether you are a European Union national or a refugee. The rest of all the people should have to follow the below procedure. if you are an immigrant then you have a chance to get a permit of driving for a year. You can practice your driving skills in France. and it would be easy for one to face all the procedures of getting a license in a better way after a year.<br>Now after a year what you should do? there are two ways here to get admission to driving school. and before going into it I will love to tell you how to get finance your driving license. one way of financing a driving license is through pole emploi and the other way is to use your CPF account.<br>Now come to point the first step to get your french driving license. Admission or registration in driving school. there are two ways as I mentioned above. one is an online registration and the other is to go to driving school locally. my experience with an online school is the best. I found Ornikar the best auto online school. you find everything online on this site and they explain it very well. no hidden charges. at the time of registration, they give you a unique id provided by the french government.<br>after taking all the lessons and making your concept clear you can go for the test. you can go for the test. you can find all details of giving the test from objectifcode website. your location, schedule for test everything is there. The price for a test is 30 euros. you can give the test unlimited time. so the pressure is on…don&#8217;t feel it… it&#8217;s the start of your journey to integrate into french society.<br>When you get passed with at least 35 marks out of 40. you will go to the next step …..Hours for driving practice. You can go to your local school or it is also available online (e.g Ornikar). they provide you expert person to practice you in the car driving. They charge you according per hour. Before getting to the hours&#8217; schedule they conduct the test to check your level of driving a car. After evaluation, they suggest you number of hours for practice. it will be a minimum of 20 hours. If you are a professional driver then it can be reduced but it&#8217;s up to your experience.<br>one your teacher though now you can go for the exam which is taken by a person given by police department of France. He/She will take the exam after evaluation one will upload the result online. minimum of two working days you can see your result online.</p>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/driving-licence-in-france/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to write a research paper</title>
		<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/</link>
					<comments>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research Article]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[How to write research article]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/?p=737</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As per the title, ‘How To Write a Research Paper’, this is how you can write a research paper – in simple language, as per the instructions given. You have to follow these steps to become an expert writer. The first step is to make sure that your topic is related to what you are &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">How to write a research paper</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As per the title, ‘How To Write a Research Paper’, this is how you can write a research paper – in simple language, as per the instructions given. You have to follow these steps to become an expert writer.</p>



<p>The first step is to make sure that your topic is related to what you are writing about. The second one is to think of at least two topics from which to choose. It may also be better if you use any credible sources. There are plenty of them available online. Once done, you need to find proper information about this topic and start researching it. Then write down all your facts and figures and do some analysis based on your thoughts. Be careful not to mention anything specific and remember that you are doing a scholarly work that has to stand out among other similar works. Lastly, you may find yourself having lots of problems with grammar and writing style. To avoid such issues, it is best to take regular classes for academic writing, especially those by experts like Harvard or Berkeley Writing Program. This will help you perfect your skills and build up your knowledge base. Furthermore, when you can get good help, your essay may be more impressive and effective. Also, you may even find ways to develop it further. You can try to improve your research paper by giving different kinds of examples, using statistics or scientific evidence from various studies. Your conclusion should discuss the key points, which you mentioned as well. The conclusion should always mention the topic that was discussed throughout the entire essay. Overall your research paper should be clear and convincing. Read our research paper examples for more tips and strategies on how to write a strong research paper. The process cannot be repeated. And to become more successful at it, follow this advice carefully.</p>



<p>Key Takeaways Before starting to come up with ideas, get a more detailed understanding of the question. Use previous studies to support your research paper. Have a particular idea of the problem you researched? Focus on keywords. A literature review, for example, needs to show which area the research may have to talk about. Make the argument at least 5 paragraphs long – this will give some room to gather relevant data. When working, keep your focus on the main point and try to connect new material with generalizations. The most important thing is to make a thesis statement that is supported by solid evidence. Stick to it and then explain it to yourself and others. Give suggestions and ideas during brainstorming sessions. When gathering thoughts, avoid over-thinking, keeping only a few ideas to write down. Start making short lists without reading more. Do not worry about the structure of your paper. Use a proper outline and stick to it. Follow the guidelines of MLA formatting, avoiding unnecessary words like “because”, “then”, “if” etc. Make notes in class; they will make your research paper stronger. Think back to your original draft before getting any feedback. Ask questions to your classmates. Remember to stay organized at all times. Plan for time management. Review past papers. What kind of tools do you have? When writing papers consider which tools should be used and how many words per page or how much research or citing you are going to do. Check out our samples for great examples of how to write an outstanding research paper or how to get help for finding expert articles online.</p>



<p>How To Format A Research Paper</p>



<p>You don’t need fancy software or complex technology to do your research paper – if you have enough knowledge and experience, just follow the format that most students and professors use. Most popularly known as the APA style, this format is commonly used by institutions for papers on psychology and education and has some significant variations.</p>



<p>You can read more about the format and examples here. Here is a sample, including details for each chapter that helps you identify and fix its flaws.</p>



<p>Chapter 1 (introductory) – include important aspects of the paper, including the goal of your paper and a brief introduction to how the topic relates to your chosen field.</p>



<p>Chapter 2 (secondary literature) – present primary research sources by talking about their arguments, findings, limitations, advantages, and disadvantages. Identify methods and frameworks used and discuss their implications. Include at least two scholarly sources discussing both the significance of social networks and the impact of Facebook on youth. If possible, show where this information was obtained and how it can affect modern society.</p>



<p>Chapter 3 (critical review) – provide background information on the topic under study and talk about its relevance, significance, and contribution to theory and practice. Provide a brief evaluation of the current state of the field and give a sense of its depth.</p>



<p>Chapter 4 (conclusions &amp; personal statement) – offer your opinion on the issue of your interest and how you think it was dealt with. How could you contribute to the future generation and how did you contribute to your school/colleague/workplace? Did you contribute to the development of contemporary thinking? Give a summary of the paper and a couple of final comments for your readers.</p>



<p>If there are no previous articles on the selected topic, list and summarize the essential information for that point. You won’t need to cite all the information from the reference list and other resources that you referred to in the body of your text.</p>



<p>Use quotation marks and correct punctuations in the paper. For example: “Facebook users can now share their photos and videos for free to their friends and family members”. Correct the spelling of the main idea. You can also add some sections at the end to the body of the report in which case, the headings will change. Annotate the paper and use headings to separate sections.</p>



<p>Try to use full citations in the body of the document. Just keep it small and straightforward. Avoid repeating your work. We love using tools and have been doing so for years. Just make sure that you check all the formats, punctuation, and correcting mistakes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>python language</title>
		<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/pythonlanguage/</link>
					<comments>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/pythonlanguage/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 08:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Programming Language]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[python]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In this post I would like to introduce you to the latest language from python programming, we name it pandas. But before that, let us look at how it can be used for various things. Pandas is a data manipulation package, specially designed for large-scale numerical data analysis and visualization. It was developed in 2009 &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/pythonlanguage/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">python language</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In this post I would like to introduce you to the latest language from python programming, we name it pandas. But before that, let us look at how it can be used for various things.</p>



<p>Pandas is a data manipulation package, specially designed for large-scale numerical data analysis and visualization. It was developed in 2009 by Wes McKinney and his graduate student Julia Sidel and was initially based on R. Pandas has been very beneficial for many different fields of research—from scientific computing to financial finance to machine learning. The primary advantage of using pandas is that it allows users to operate with huge amounts of data without having to worry about memory or storage space. Let’s start our discussion by using pandas for beginners and then move on moving forward.</p>



<p>Pandas help read and write to a few files, which are table-like lists and dictionaries. For example, we can use pandas to read the following file named ‘test.csv’. You need to import pandas after reading the CSV file. So first I will do this firstly, but not only that you need to use this code later, but you also need to import certain packages as well.</p>



<p>The second code is importing ‘NumPy’. Now if you don’t know what is numpy and why we need to import it then follow my article on what is Numpy &amp; How Can We Use It. A brief introduction to numpy and other essential libraries used in the field of Machine Learning.</p>



<p>Now we will try to understand some data that is stored in this CSV file. First, let us create two datasets using pandas.</p>



<p>Let us call the test.csv dataset the x_train dataset and y_train dataset.</p>



<p>The x_train dataset contains an array called features. Features are a list of two columns, we can see these two variables in the x_train file. Our goal here is to get details of the variables and make them independent. Let’s create another CSV file named training.csv.</p>



<p>Now let us create the training CSV file.</p>



<p>Now we will print the entire feature column names and their values in train.csv.</p>



<p>What do we observe from these two files? The variable ‘x’ is the original one, and the second one is the target variable; so it is not something random. I already have done all the above steps, but we still can change the values and make them dependent variables. If you want to know more about dependent and independent variables then check this great article from Stack Overflow. Here we are considering both kinds of variables.</p>



<p>Let us write a script to write down the value of the target and then use it to calculate the score given by X and y. Then the score can be displayed as output in a text box. I will show you below the code I did.</p>



<p>This script should give us the output:</p>



<p>That’s it!</p>



<p>Now, let&#8217;s execute the above codes in the terminal. Remember this is the last step in coding. We have to run the code in the terminal. Do you see any errors here? Yes, no errors.</p>



<p>Now let us execute these codes from the command line.</p>



<p>We get the same result as we saw earlier.</p>



<p>Conclusion</p>



<h1 class="has-small-font-size">Pandas is a very useful library for analyzing data. There are many tutorials on where to find information for different types of problems to get the best results. After you get into Python programming you must always remember the basics and stay away from making mistakes. This is because most beginner programmers forget the fundamental concepts first. I hope now you got a feel of Pandas. I will keep updating articles in this blog regarding more important topics mentioned earlier in this blog and others.</h1>



<h1>python language</h1>



<p>In this post I would like to introduce you to the latest language from python programming, we name it pandas. But before that, let us look at how it can be used for various things.</p>



<p>Pandas is a data manipulation package, specially designed for large-scale numerical data analysis and visualization. It was developed in 2009 by Wes McKinney and his graduate student Julia Sidel and was initially based on R. Pandas has been very beneficial for many different fields of research—from scientific computing to financial finance to machine learning. The primary advantage of using pandas is that it allows users to operate with huge amounts of data without having to worry about memory or storage space. Let’s start our discussion by using pandas for beginners and then move on moving forward.</p>



<p>Pandas help read and write to a few files, which are table-like lists and dictionaries. For example, we can use pandas to read the following file named ‘test.csv’. You need to import pandas after reading the CSV file. So first I will do this firstly, but not only that you need to use this code later, but you also need to import certain packages as well.</p>



<p>The second code is importing ‘numpy’. Now if you don’t know what is numpy and why we need to import it then follow my article on what is numpy &amp; How Can We Use It. A brief introduction to numpy and other essential libraries used in the field of Machine Learning.</p>



<p>Now we will try to understand some data that is stored in this CSV file. First, let us create two datasets using pandas.</p>



<p>Let us call the test.csv dataset the x_train dataset and y_train dataset.</p>



<p>The x_train dataset contains an array called features. Features are a list of two columns, we can see these two variables in the x_train file. Our goal here is to get details of the variables and make them independent. Let’s create another CSV file named training.csv.</p>



<p>Now let us create the training CSV file.</p>



<p>Now we will print the entire feature column names and their values in train.csv.</p>



<p>What do we observe from these two files? The variable ‘x’ is the original one, and the second one is the target variable; so it is not something random. I already have done all the above steps, but we still can change the values and make them dependent variables. If you want to know more about dependent and independent variables then check this great article from Stack Overflow. Here we are considering both kinds of variables.</p>



<p>Let us write a script to write down the value of the target and then use it to calculate the score given by X and y. Then the score can be displayed as output in a text box. I will show you below the code I did.</p>



<p>This script should give us the output:</p>



<p>That’s it!</p>



<p>Now, let&#8217;s execute the above codes in the terminal. Remember this is the last step in coding. We have to run the code in the terminal. Do you see any errors here? Yes, no errors.</p>



<p>Now let us execute these codes from the command line.</p>



<p>We get the same result as we saw earlier.</p>



<p>Conclusion</p>



<h1 class="has-text-align-left has-medium-font-size" style="text-transform:lowercase">Pandas is a very useful library for analyzing data. There are many tutorials on where to find information for different types of problems to get the best results. After you get into Python programming you must always remember the basics and stay away from making mistakes. This is because most beginner programmers forget the fundamental concepts first. I hope now you got a feel of Pandas. I will keep updating articles in this blog regarding more important topics mentioned earlier in this blog and others.</h1>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/pythonlanguage/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
