<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Tech Smasher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Aug 2022 12:03:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.8.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Getting Driving Licence in France</title>
		<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/driving-licence-in-france/</link>
					<comments>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/driving-licence-in-france/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 09:34:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[General]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/?p=795</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[French Drivers Need More Experience Than British Drivers but don&#8217;t take their driver&#8217;s test too seriously: The state of affairs is still not that great concerning road tests. But, there are some different approaches to this. The first and most common method for getting driving licenses in France is divided into two categories. One is &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/driving-licence-in-france/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Getting Driving Licence in France</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>French Drivers Need More Experience Than British Drivers but don&#8217;t take their driver&#8217;s test too seriously: The state of affairs is still not that great concerning road tests. But, there are some different approaches to this.</p>



<p>The first and most common method for getting driving licenses in France is divided into two categories. One is AAC (Apprentisage accompagnée Conduite) other is accompagnée. drive more than 3,000 km over at least a year, guided by one or more guides, whether or not from the family (parents). Indeed, although it is not an obligation, it is the parents who, most of the time, supervise their child. But the AAC guide can also be another member of the family or even an outside person but holding a French license for a minimum of five years. There are some methods which you won’t find on all roads. However, they are available in case you want something else. You can call any test center or even apply online.<br>There are two ways your driving license can be changed whether you are a European Union national or a refugee. The rest of all the people should have to follow the below procedure. if you are an immigrant then you have a chance to get a permit of driving for a year. You can practice your driving skills in France. and it would be easy for one to face all the procedures of getting a license in a better way after a year.<br>Now after a year what you should do? there are two ways here to get admission to driving school. and before going into it I will love to tell you how to get finance your driving license. one way of financing a driving license is through pole emploi and the other way is to use your CPF account.<br>Now come to point the first step to get your french driving license. Admission or registration in driving school. there are two ways as I mentioned above. one is an online registration and the other is to go to driving school locally. my experience with an online school is the best. I found Ornikar the best auto online school. you find everything online on this site and they explain it very well. no hidden charges. at the time of registration, they give you a unique id provided by the french government.<br>after taking all the lessons and making your concept clear you can go for the test. you can go for the test. you can find all details of giving the test from objectifcode website. your location, schedule for test everything is there. The price for a test is 30 euros. you can give the test unlimited time. so the pressure is on…don&#8217;t feel it… it&#8217;s the start of your journey to integrate into french society.<br>When you get passed with at least 35 marks out of 40. you will go to the next step …..Hours for driving practice. You can go to your local school or it is also available online (e.g Ornikar). they provide you expert person to practice you in the car driving. They charge you according per hour. Before getting to the hours&#8217; schedule they conduct the test to check your level of driving a car. After evaluation, they suggest you number of hours for practice. it will be a minimum of 20 hours. If you are a professional driver then it can be reduced but it&#8217;s up to your experience.<br>one your teacher though now you can go for the exam which is taken by a person given by police department of France. He/She will take the exam after evaluation one will upload the result online. minimum of two working days you can see your result online.</p>



<p></p>



<p></p>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/driving-licence-in-france/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What is Research Article</title>
		<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/what-is-research-article/</link>
					<comments>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/what-is-research-article/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:23:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research Article]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/?p=737</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A research article is a primary source&#8230;that is, it reports the methods and results of an original study performed by the authors. &#8230; A brief introduction will often include a review of the existing literature on the topic studied, and explain the rationale of the author&#8217;s study.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A research article is <strong>a primary source</strong>&#8230;that is, it reports the methods and results of an original study performed by the authors. &#8230; A brief introduction will often include a review of the existing literature on the topic studied, and explain the rationale of the author&#8217;s study.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/what-is-research-article/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Research Article</title>
		<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/</link>
					<comments>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 11:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research Article]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/?p=734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A research article is a primary source&#8230;that is, it reports the methods and results of an original study performed by the authors. &#8230; A brief introduction will often include a review of the existing literature on the topic studied, and explain the rationale of the author&#8217;s study.]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A research article is <strong>a primary source</strong>&#8230;that is, it reports the methods and results of an original study performed by the authors. &#8230; A brief introduction will often include a review of the existing literature on the topic studied, and explain the rationale of the author&#8217;s study.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Python Tutorial</title>
		<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Nov 2021 08:59:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Programming Language]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Python tutorials for developers of all skill levels, Python books and courses, Python news, code examples, articles, and more. The real python tutorial covers almost most of the python programming tricks, techniques, and latest improvements. At Real Python, you can learn all things Python from the ground up. If you want to get short &#38; &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/hello-world/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">Python Tutorial</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Python tutorials for developers of all skill levels, Python books and courses, Python news, code examples, articles, and more. The real python tutorial covers almost most of the python programming tricks, techniques, and latest improvements. At Real Python, you can learn all things Python from the ground up. If you want to get short &amp; sweet Python Trick delivered to your inbox every couple of days, you can subscribe to their newsletter.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
