<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Research Article &#8211; Tech Smasher</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/category/research-article/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 14:51:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>How to write a research paper</title>
		<link>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/</link>
					<comments>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 18 Aug 2022 14:20:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Research Article]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[research article]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/?p=737</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[As per the title, ‘How To Write a Research Paper’, this is how you can write a research paper – in simple language, as per the instructions given. You have to follow these steps to become an expert writer. The first step is to make sure that your topic is related to what you are &#8230;<p class="read-more"> <a class="" href="https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/"> <span class="screen-reader-text">How to write a research paper</span> Read More &#187;</a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>As per the title, ‘How To Write a Research Paper’, this is how you can write a research paper – in simple language, as per the instructions given. You have to follow these steps to become an expert writer.</p>



<p>The first step is to make sure that your topic is related to what you are writing about. The second one is to think of at least two topics from which to choose. It may also be better if you use any credible sources. There are plenty of them available online. Once done, you need to find proper information about this topic and start researching it. Then write down all your facts and figures and do some analysis based on your thoughts. Be careful not to mention anything specific and remember that you are doing a scholarly work that has to stand out among other similar works. Lastly, you may find yourself having lots of problems with grammar and writing style. To avoid such issues, it is best to take regular classes for academic writing, especially those by experts like Harvard or Berkeley Writing Program. This will help you perfect your skills and build up your knowledge base. Furthermore, when you can get good help, your essay may be more impressive and effective. Also, you may even find ways to develop it further. You can try to improve your research paper by giving different kinds of examples, using statistics or scientific evidence from various studies. Your conclusion should discuss the key points, which you mentioned as well. The conclusion should always mention the topic that was discussed throughout the entire essay. Overall your research paper should be clear and convincing. Read our research paper examples for more tips and strategies on how to write a strong research paper. The process cannot be repeated. And to become more successful at it, follow this advice carefully.</p>



<p>Key Takeaways Before starting to come up with ideas, get a more detailed understanding of the question. Use previous studies to support your research paper. Have a particular idea of the problem you researched? Focus on keywords. A literature review, for example, needs to show which area the research may have to talk about. Make the argument at least 5 paragraphs long – this will give some room to gather relevant data. When working, keep your focus on the main point and try to connect new material with generalizations. The most important thing is to make a thesis statement that is supported by solid evidence. Stick to it and then explain it to yourself and others. Give suggestions and ideas during brainstorming sessions. When gathering thoughts, avoid over-thinking, keeping only a few ideas to write down. Start making short lists without reading more. Do not worry about the structure of your paper. Use a proper outline and stick to it. Follow the guidelines of MLA formatting, avoiding unnecessary words like “because”, “then”, “if” etc. Make notes in class; they will make your research paper stronger. Think back to your original draft before getting any feedback. Ask questions to your classmates. Remember to stay organized at all times. Plan for time management. Review past papers. What kind of tools do you have? When writing papers consider which tools should be used and how many words per page or how much research or citing you are going to do. Check out our samples for great examples of how to write an outstanding research paper or how to get help for finding expert articles online.</p>



<p>How To Format A Research Paper</p>



<p>You don’t need fancy software or complex technology to do your research paper – if you have enough knowledge and experience, just follow the format that most students and professors use. Most popularly known as the APA style, this format is commonly used by institutions for papers on psychology and education and has some significant variations.</p>



<p>You can read more about the format and examples here. Here is a sample, including details for each chapter that helps you identify and fix its flaws.</p>



<p>Chapter 1 (introductory) – include important aspects of the paper, including the goal of your paper and a brief introduction to how the topic relates to your chosen field.</p>



<p>Chapter 2 (secondary literature) – present primary research sources by talking about their arguments, findings, limitations, advantages, and disadvantages. Identify methods and frameworks used and discuss their implications. Include at least two scholarly sources discussing both the significance of social networks and the impact of Facebook on youth. If possible, show where this information was obtained and how it can affect modern society.</p>



<p>Chapter 3 (critical review) – provide background information on the topic under study and talk about its relevance, significance, and contribution to theory and practice. Provide a brief evaluation of the current state of the field and give a sense of its depth.</p>



<p>Chapter 4 (conclusions &amp; personal statement) – offer your opinion on the issue of your interest and how you think it was dealt with. How could you contribute to the future generation and how did you contribute to your school/colleague/workplace? Did you contribute to the development of contemporary thinking? Give a summary of the paper and a couple of final comments for your readers.</p>



<p>If there are no previous articles on the selected topic, list and summarize the essential information for that point. You won’t need to cite all the information from the reference list and other resources that you referred to in the body of your text.</p>



<p>Use quotation marks and correct punctuations in the paper. For example: “Facebook users can now share their photos and videos for free to their friends and family members”. Correct the spelling of the main idea. You can also add some sections at the end to the body of the report in which case, the headings will change. Annotate the paper and use headings to separate sections.</p>



<p>Try to use full citations in the body of the document. Just keep it small and straightforward. Avoid repeating your work. We love using tools and have been doing so for years. Just make sure that you check all the formats, punctuation, and correcting mistakes.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wajeehafarooqi.github.io/techsmash.github.io/research-article/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
